Get out of my way!
Bastard!
Wait, bastard!
Help!
A guy with knife is chasing me.
Get out of my way!
Lower the knife!
I'll kill you!
He's a pervert!
I can explain.
I'm a reporter from the Meicho.
Then why were you asking
my wife
about her panties?
Excuse me,
I'd like to make an appointment
to see your listing in Shibuya.
Miss, acquiring
property in Tokyo
is a very complicated endeavor.
Yes, I'm aware of that.
Could we set an appointment
for tomorrow?
I'm afraid there are many
steps that must be taken.
I've taken those steps.
I'd like to see the space.
I'm afraid
the owner of that space
wouldn't be interested
in renting to you.
I see...
Then I'll find someone who is.
Thank you for your time.
Panty thief?
Thank you.
Rewrite it.
Yes. Will do.
No good.
Alright, you worthless
piece of shit.
Let's try this again.
You're crossing the street,
minding your own business,
when this jogger comes out of
nowhere and slams into you...
And?
What then?
What do you want me to say?
The truth. In your words.
The victim had an accidental
run-in with a thug.
Wrong place, wrong time.
Funaki, you don't really
believe that.
We have his prints on the
knife and a signed deposition.
What more do you want?
A low level Tozawa goon
just walks in off the street
and gives himself up?
Feels like the fastest way
to kill an investigation.
Investigation?
Our job is to clear cases.
This is going in.
That's the third shop
in the last month.
All under our protection.
Tozawa.
He's trying to prove
we can't protect our territory.
We have to hit back.
And risk war?
But this is war.
We hit back,
Chikara-kai will be seen
as the instigators,
and the cops
will come down on us.
Are you idiots?!
No. No retaliation.
For now, we increase
protection fees.
We use the extra money
to close ranks and prepare.
Kume,
Kobayashi...
if a war is coming
with Tozawa, we'll be ready.
Oyabun likes them
chopped fine.
Tip stays on the board,
one smooth motion...
Damn, Sato.
You think
maybe you went
into the wrong business?
Hope you're as good with that
knife outside the kitchen.
Should we go find out?
Go make the rounds.
They've already paid
this month.
Now they're paying more.
Okay.
Don't fuck up the onions.
Considering the evidence,
and now this confession,
we expect an easy conviction.
I hope this will bring
you and your family
some measure of comfort.
Forgive me if this is
too painful to revisit but...
I understand,
from the statement
you gave Detective Funaki
that your husband
was having financial problems.
I went through all this
with the other detectives.
They didn't seem
to think it was relevant.
Of course.
I'm just following up to ensure
nothing's been overlooked.
We borrowed.
Too much.
We missed one payment
and the interest rate
became ten times higher.
So my husband pushed back.
How so?
He was gathering information
to bring to a lawyer.
About these lenders
and their...
methods.
Do you happen to have
that information?
Yes.
May I help you?
My name is Jake Adelstein.
I'm with the Meicho Shimbun.
I'm sorry, I've been asked
not to speak with the press.
Really?
But...
just a few minutes is enough.
May I have some of your time?
I'm afraid I have company...
Takahiro Aoki has borrowed
a large amount of money.
How do you feel
about a dirtbag like him
living in your neighborhood?
Well, then,
can I ask you one--
I have nothing to share.
I will come again.
I'm sorry for bothering you.
Once again,
my deepest condolences.
Hey, he looks like
real yakuza, right?
Wanna play?
He's gonna kill this.
With my humble regards.
Malee, hurry up.
I don't have much time today--
Go home, Samantha.
Those things stink.
They're French.
I see that.
A trendy actor, yeah?
You got nice hair,
like an actor's.
Gaijin!
Read this. Out loud. Now.
Yes.
Underwear thief...captured...
Today at 12:30 p.m.,
the Shinjuku police arrested an
office worker, age forty-one,
a resident of Shinjuku-ward
Kabuki-cho Block 1,
on charges of theft.
The police raided his apartment
and found
400 pairs of women's underwear,
color-coded and sorted.
But according to you,
there is no underwear thief.
We can't trust you
to report one simple story.
That's why you're shit.
Go to scrapbooking.
You're done here.
Last time I checked,
Katagiri,
loan sharks don't kill people,
because dead men pay no debts.
You don't find it suspicious?
That just before filing
a lawsuit against the lender,
the man is murdered
by a low-level yakuza?
We've been
down this road before.
Or don't you remember?
Ohara-san, this is different.
Sure.
The difference is this case
has a deposition,
a murder weapon,
and a violent criminal
behind bars.
It's closed.
Thanks.
Racist nationalist.
You've got those too, right?
Move.
Sorry.
(in Korean) Yeah.
You heard me. I said shut up.
(in Korean) What part of that
don't you understand?
(in Korean)
Shut the fuck up! Right now!
(in Korean) No...no...don't
you...don't you look at me!
(in Korean) Did you hear me!
Don't you fucking look at me!
Check out Yuta!
Looks like he needs
to take a dump!
Fuck you. Fuck all of you.
I'm back.
Please check these.
Who's short?
Duke.
Said he'd have it next month.
All that money going through
the club every night,
he can't cough up
an extra hundred thousand?
You're sure he didn't offer you
house credit in the meantime?
Some shit about how,
"You could have
a good time here
with the girl of your choice?"
What the fuck
are you looking at?
Sorry.
Don't ever lie to me again.
If I don't get a real story
as soon as possible,
I'm gonna get fired.
What's that supposed to mean?
So good.
Excuse me.
Coming.
Yes?
Another of everything.
And an extra serving
of short ribs.
Extra serving.
Delicious, eh?
Excuse me.
You're leaving?
We're busy today, huh?
Cute tie!
Hurry up, will you?
Sorry.
Hey!
What the fuck
are you sitting down for?
Table 7.
Go!
Where's my Imperial Brut?
I've been waiting a while.
One moment.
Excuse me, here's the check.
Let's raise our glasses.
Excuse me. Samantha,
you are being requested.
All right.
If you'll excuse me...
I'm very sorry.
Here's Nana instead.
That blonde girl, Samantha.
Sure. This way.
She will be right with you.
Excuse me.
You have a customer.
You know what to do.
You came alone this time.
Gives us a chance to chat.
Finally.
You're a glutton
for punishment, aren't you?
Tattoo...
Cool kicks.
Excuse me...
Hey!
From America.
Counterfeit.
Really?
This is today's last train.
Please hurry.
Hang in there.
Who's that?
No one.
This is an urgent announcement
from the Police Department.
An organized crime incident
has been reported
in the Shinjuku precinct.
Possibility of crime involving
the use of firearms or knives.
Effective for Shinjuku,
Yotsuya,
and Harajuku precincts.
Crime scene located
at Kabuchiko,
District 4, Lot 1,
Building 2, IDS building...
Shut the fuck up!
Try me if you got the balls.
I'll fucking shoot you!
- Nakamura, put the gun down!
- Don't, Nakamura.
Wait.
We--we can talk about it.
Please, let me explain.
This is who you pay
to protect you?
These Chihara-kai punks
can't protect shit!
Listen.
We go where we want,
we drink where we want!
This district, this city...
belongs to Tozawa now.
You tell Ishida that.
Just shoot him.
Fuck it.
Nakamura!
Nice watch.
Thanks.
From Hong Kong.
Looks as good as a real one.
Hey.
Meicho reporter...I see.
Your camera.
You hear me?